(Q1) Good evening. King's Restaurant.
Good evening. I'm ringing about the job I understand you have vacant.
Oh yes.
I'd like to find out a few more details, if I may.
Yes, of course. Can I take your name?
It's Peter Chin.
Okay Peter. Well, if you want to ask about the job and then if we're both still interested, we could arrange for you to come for an interview.
Great, thanks. I'm afraid I missed the advert for the job but heard about it from a friend.
That's no problem at all. What would you like to know?
[🟢 定位] Well, um, what sort of work is it - washing up?
[Q1答案句] It's answering the phone.
Oh right, fine.
And not waiting at table.
(Q2) That'd be good. And how many nights a week would it be?
Well, we're really only busy at the weekend.
So two nights?
Three actually, so it would work out at twelve hours a week.
That'd be fine. It wouldn't interfere with my studies.
Are you at the university?
Yes. First year Physics student.
Oh, right.
Um, and because I'm not an EU national would I need a work permit?
Yes you would. Just get your tutor to sign it.
That wouldn't be a problem, if I were to get the job. Um, where exactly is the restaurant?
Well, we have two branches - the one we're recruiting for is in Hillsdunne Road.
I don't know that. How do you spell it please?
[Q2答案句] It's H-I-double L-S-D-U-double N-E Road.
(Q3) Got that. Thanks. Is it near a bus stop?
[Q3答案句] Yes. The nearest one would probably be just beside the Library.
(Q4) Oh yes, I know it. That'd be fine for me. And could I ask about the pay?
[Q4答案句] We're offering £4.45 an hour.
That's very good. My last job was £3.95 an hour.
(Q5) We feel it's pretty good and we also offer some good fringe benefits.
Really?
Well, we give you a free dinner, so you eat well.
Right, better than hostel food!
[Q5答案句] We certainly hope so! And we also offer extra pay for working on national holidays.
(Q6) Oh, that's a really good perk, isn't it?
[Q6答案句] Yes, we think so. And then because of the difficulties of getting public transport, if you're working after 11 o'clock we drive you home.
Oh, that's good to know.
(Q7) Well, we'd certainly be interested in inviting you for an interview, if you're still interested?
Oh yes, certainly. Could I just also ask what qualities you're looking for?
[Q7答案句] Well, for this particular job we want a clear voice, which you obviously do have!
Thanks.
(Q8) [Q8答案句] And you must be able to think quickly, you know.
Well, I hope I'd.
(Q9) So, when could you come in for an interview? We're actually quite quiet tonight?
[Q9答案句] Sorry, I couldn't come tonight. Or tomorrow, I'm afraid. Thursday's okay - that'd be 22nd of October.
Fine, after 5 p.m.?
Yes, fine. Would 6 o'clock be okay?
(Q10) Perfect. And could you bring along with the names of two referees?
Yes, that's fine, no problem.
Good, I look forward to seeing you.
Oh, by the way, who should I ask for?
Oh yes, of course, sorry. My name is Samira Manuja.
Can you spell that, please?
[Q10答案句] M-A-N-U-J-A.
Okay, I've got that. Thanks very much.
Look forward to seeing you…